=My Sweet Professor= =Episode 7=
= أستاذي الحلو = = الحلقة 7 =
Hello?
مرحبًا؟
Dr. Gao.
دكتور جاو.
Are you free this evening?
هل أنت متفرغ هذا المساء؟
Let's have dinner tonight.
لنتناول العشاء الليلة.
Huo Shang?
هوه شانغ؟
Mm.
مم.
I'm on duty tonight. I'm afraid I won't have time.
أنا في الخدمة الليلة.  أخشى أنه لن يكون لدي وقت.
Hey.
يا.
I'm at the door of your hospital.
أنا على باب المستشفى الخاص بك.
And Dr. Gao,
والدكتور جاو ،
I forgot to tell you.
نسيت أن أخبرك.
I have a copy of your duty roster.
لدي نسخة من قائمة المناوبات الخاصة بك.
Are you ready, Dr. Gao?
هل أنت جاهز يا دكتور جاو؟
Why hasn't he come down?
لماذا لم ينزل؟
Dr. Gao.
دكتور جاو.
Dr. Gao has left.
غادر الدكتور جاو.
When did he leave?
متى غادر؟
About an hour ago.
منذ ساعة تقريبا.
Shoot. I forgot about the back door.
أطلق النار.  لقد نسيت الباب الخلفي.
Gao Yuan.
جاو يوان.
I know you're in there.
أعلم أنك هناك.
How did you get in?
كيف تحصل في؟
I came through the door.
جئت من الباب.
Where did you get the key?
من أين لك المفتاح؟
I didn't.
لم أكن.
Huo Shang.
هوه شانغ.
I'm begging you.
أتوسل إليك.
We have our own lives now.
لدينا حياتنا الآن.
You live your life
أنت تعيش حياتك
and I live mine.
وأنا أعيش ملكي.
Alright?
على ما يرام؟
No.
رقم.
Why are you avoiding me?
لماذا تتجنبني؟
I'm not.
أنالست.
Don't you wanna know what I've been through for the last eight years?
ألا تريد أن تعرف ما مررت به خلال السنوات الثماني الماضية؟
I don't.
أنا لا.
I don't wanna know what you've been through.
لا أريد أن أعرف ما مررت به.
And I don't wanna know why you left.
ولا أريد أن أعرف سبب مغادرتك.
Stop talking about the past.
توقف عن الحديث عن الماضي.
I don't want to know anything about what happened before.
لا أريد أن أعرف أي شيء عما حدث من قبل.
Is that okay?
هل هذا مقبول؟
Listen to this question.
استمع إلى هذا السؤال.
Which of the following statement about human tissue fluid is wrong?
أي العبارات التالية خاطئة عن سوائل الأنسجة البشرية؟
Option A.
الخيار أ.
Glucose from plasma
الجلوكوز من البلازما
can enter skeletal muscle cells through tissue fluid.
يمكن أن تدخل خلايا العضلات والهيكل العظمي من خلال سوائل الأنسجة.
Wanna play Gobang?
تريد أن تلعب Gobang؟
There are so many questions left.
هناك الكثير من الأسئلة المتبقية.
Can you hold on a little longer?
هل يمكنك التمسك لفترة أطول قليلاً؟
Option A must be right.
يجب أن يكون الخيار "أ" صحيحًا.
And Option B.
والخيار ب.
Carbon dioxide produced by respiration metabolism of stem cells...
ينتج ثاني أكسيد الكربون عن طريق التمثيل الغذائي التنفسي للخلايا الجذعية ...
Do you wanna play?
هل تريد أن تلعب؟
Who goes first?
الذي يذهب أولا؟
You.
أنت.
♪ As long as you're here ♪
♪ ما دمت هنا ♪
One more round.
جوله اخرى.
♪ My heart pounds every time when you're around ♪
♪ قلبي ينبض في كل مرة عندما تكون بالجوار ♪
You lost again.
لقد خسرت مرة أخرى.
No way, let's play again.
بأي حال من الأحوال ، لنلعب مرة أخرى.
You're so smart,
انت ذكي جدا
but how can't you win me at Gobang?
ولكن كيف لا يمكنك الفوز بي في Gobang؟
Don't look down on me.
لا تنظر إلي باستخفاف.
Let's play one more round.
لنلعب جولة أخرى.
If I win, you should study all the questions with me.
إذا فزت ، يجب أن تدرس معي جميع الأسئلة.
Mm.
مم.
=My Sweet Professor=
= أستاذي الحلو =